bestsearchdirectory.com 2016-09-22

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or enter information on our site.

### How do we use your information? 

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

      To improve our website in order to better serve you.

### How do we protect visitor information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

We do not use an SSL certificate

      **•** We do not need an SSL because:

we are store personal data

### Do we use 'cookies'?

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

However, you can still place orders .

### Third-party disclosure

Do we disclose the information we collect to Third-Parties?

We sell,trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties any form or online contact identifier email, name of chat account etc. personally identifiable information.

### Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf  

### According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:

      **•** On our Privacy Policy Page

Users are able to change their personal information:

      **•** By emailing us

      **•** By logging in to their account

### How does our site handle do not track signals?

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. 

### Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?

It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

### Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

We will notify the users via email

      **•** Within 1 business day

We will notify the users via in-site notification

      **•** Within 1 business day

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

### We collect your email address in order to:

      **•** Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

      **•** Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.

      **•** We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.

      **•** Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

### To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:

      **•** NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

      **•** Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

      **•** Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

      **•** Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

      **•** Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

      **•** Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

### If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at

http://www.bestsearchdirectory.com/contact and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

### **Refund Policy**

 **Our company is very particular about any feedback from the purchasers of our services. If you send us a message informing about an error, any question or just a suggestion, you will receive a fast and competent answer from our technical support team within 24 working hours. As a rule all the majority of problems are solved "on the spot". Numerous positive reports concerning our specialists and services prove that perfectly well. **We provides refund of your payment in the following cases:** **1.** If you accidentally bought the product more than once for the same URL.  
**2.** If you intend to cancel your order before start of the service.

**We reserve the right to decline refund requests in the following cases:** **1.** When a user demands a refund immediately after receiving the service/ report.  
**2.** When a user informs us about changing his decision to buy the service , saying he is not going to use the service's contents after receiving it.  
**3.** When reasons which prevent a customer from proper using of the service are stated clearly on our official site. (For example, if the customer requests a refund due to the absence of features which we never claimed to provide and which are not listed in the feature list for the product). 

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.bestsearchdirectory.com/contact 

Last Edited on 2016-05-30

**
